webwiz.co.uk 2012-09-20

# Web Wiz Data Protection and Privacy Policy

|    

'Web Wiz' is committed to respecting the privacy of individuals who use the 'Web Wiz' websites and operate and are registered under the The UK Data Protection Act, registration number Z2859497, you can view the full Privacy Statement below. 

  1. **Please find below our privacy policy for 'Web Wiz'**  
We are 'Web Wiz Ltd' a company registered in England & Wales (Company Reg. 5977755) and our registered address is Unit 10E Dawkins Road Industrial Estate, Poole, Dorset, England. Web Wiz takes the privacy of its customers data very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal data after it has been collected by us through your use of this website.
  2. **When do we collect data?**  
We can collect data on you from a variety of different sources these include. 
    1. When you purchase products or services from the site or via any of our other distribution channels. 
    2. When you become a subscriber;
    3. When you enter data into a form on the website; 
    4. When you speak to our customer services personnel; 
    5. When you activate your product via our License Activation Server 
    6. Via explicit data capture measures, for example by entering competitions, completing surveys, registering products, registering to use the support forum; 
    7. Via implicit data capture measures such as studying which pages you read the most and the use of cookies. 
  
In any of the above cases the data we collect could be personal data.
  3. **What do we do with your personal information?**  
When you buy anything via the site or give us any personal data as indicated above, we may need to collect information about you to process the transaction, fulfil your order and provide you with the services you expect then and in the future. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address, your phone number. 

Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to third parties if this is required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us. This is of course subject to the proviso that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as members of our own group, our own professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data. 

By becoming a subscriber you consent to receive from us by email our eNewsletters and details of other special offers or services which we may think may be of interest to you. 

'Web Wiz' retains and uses your personal information to provide you with the remote commerce (including electronic and mobile commerce) experience by providing you with a personalised service and to give you details of offers which we think will be of interest to you and keep you informed of changes to products, services, licenses agreements, terms, conditions, and security updates. We may also use the information to process any transactions you undertake with us and for internal administration and analysis.

We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties. 

  4. **Public Information; Forum, Guestbook, Directories**  
By their very nature the Forum, Guestbook, Listing Directories, etc. are open to the public, any information given will be viewable to the general public. 'Web Wiz' does make every effort to keep details such as email addresses private, but if you do select to have your email address shown it will be viewable by the general public.
  5. **Children’s Privacy**  
'Web Wiz' is committed to keeping the details of children private by following the guidelines setout in the US, C.O.P.P.A Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

'Web Wiz' does not collect private information from children under the age of 13 without written permission from the child’s parents of guardians. If you are under the age of 13 or you have a child under this age who wishes to use areas of the site that require some level or personal information be given then please send written permission first to, Web Wiz, Unit 10E Dawkins Road Industrial Estate, Poole, Dorset, England.

Parents or guardians that find that their children have given private information in accessing any parts of 'Web Wiz' can request that this information be destroyed by emailing using the contact us form. 

  6. **Cookies**  
Each website owned and operated by 'Web Wiz' uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file of which there are two types:  
**  
Session cookies:** These are used to maintain something called session state. If you consider your journey through the site to be a conversation with us and this cookie just reminds the site where we were in that conversation. These are required for the site to function for example when you login into client or forum areas of the website or make a purchase. 

**Permanent cookies:** These store data on your hard drive. You can view them by looking in the cookies directory of your browser installation if you are interested. They last for a long time and each time you come to our site you send us a copy of them. We use them to identify you between visits. For instance when you login into the support or community forums a cookie is created to maintain your login to the system. 

You can block cookies but they are required for certain parts if the site to work correctly and will enhance your experience when using the web site. 

  7. **Data**  
In the UK we operate and are registered in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.
  8. **Consent**  
By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by 'Web Wiz' in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. Some information and emails sent to 'Web Wiz' may be used as testimonials but no email address or contact details will be displayed.
  9. **Change/Modify Details**  
If you need to Modify or Change your personal details after you have made a purchase or registered to use certain parts of the website please contact us as soon as possible.
  10. **Contact**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, you can also contact us.

|
